<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>YouTube Journey on Leslie TANG</title>
    <link>https://leslietang.com/categories/youtube-journey/</link>
    <description>Recent content in YouTube Journey on Leslie TANG</description>
    <image>
      <url>https://leslietang.com/papermod-cover.png</url>
      <link>https://leslietang.com/papermod-cover.png</link>
    </image>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 21 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://leslietang.com/categories/youtube-journey/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>How to Grow Channels</title>
      <link>https://leslietang.com/posts/how-to-grow-channels/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://leslietang.com/posts/how-to-grow-channels/</guid>
      <description>Reference: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=gyr0hQatckE&amp;amp;ab_channel=ChannelMakers
Valuable Ideas valuable, appealing ideas, that would attract viewers. i.e. VIEWS are the absolute metrics that will indicate which videos are doing well.
Concrete Steps
 Create various videos, with different ideas see which one performs best Improve on the good performing videos  Common Mistake
 no subscribability factor  Pick One Thing to Improve After each video. improve by 1%. recall atomic habits. Pay attention to the Average View Duration.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My understanding of the 3 act structure</title>
      <link>https://leslietang.com/posts/my-understanding-of-the-3-act-structure/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://leslietang.com/posts/my-understanding-of-the-3-act-structure/</guid>
      <description>Setup The purpose is to set up the story. The wrap up of this part, is when the protaganist needs to make a decision.
Beginning The background, context.
Inciting Incident A single trigger that cause the start of the journey. A strong pain. A strong trigger. An event.
Basically, something happens and the underlying context is affected. The peace is disturbed. Or something like that.
Second Thoughts Reference: https://philipp.truebiger.com/three-act-structure/#:~:text=Second%20Thoughts%3A,to%20the%20farm%20and%20work.
The protaganist needs to make a decision.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why Video Edit</title>
      <link>https://leslietang.com/posts/why-video-edit/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://leslietang.com/posts/why-video-edit/</guid>
      <description>Set Up. Why did I start learning about video editing?
 Seems fun It&amp;rsquo;s a core skill that would be useful for a YouTube channel I want to start a channel for the side income potential Video edit is the core part, which seems so daunting and difficult, so I wanted to try something low stakes and fun. Just to get a taste.  At the core of things, I just want to make money through side hustle, that is decoupled from my time.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
