<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Adobe Premiere Pro on Leslie TANG</title>
    <link>https://leslietang.com/categories/adobe-premiere-pro/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Adobe Premiere Pro on Leslie TANG</description>
    <image>
      <url>https://leslietang.com/papermod-cover.png</url>
      <link>https://leslietang.com/papermod-cover.png</link>
    </image>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 25 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://leslietang.com/categories/adobe-premiere-pro/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>1 Week of Creating Videos</title>
      <link>https://leslietang.com/posts/self-reflection-after-1-week/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://leslietang.com/posts/self-reflection-after-1-week/</guid>
      <description>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=02SSBjKI4kE&amp;amp;ab_channel=LearningRandomStuffs
After watching my video with fresh eyes. I can say with conviction that this is trash.
I would click away without thoughts.
What do I need to improve?
A clearer message. A more compelling reason for viewers to watch. The hook.
What is the value proposition of this video? There are 3 main points in the video.
 Reframing a difficult task  Alternative Phrasing  Expect nothing Don&amp;rsquo;t expect anything Don&amp;rsquo;t expect results immediately Reframe into long term perspective Be realistic but hold the unrealistic dream close to your heart     Simplify the process Reflect and iterate  Credibility These 3 steps, when they come together, should enable someone to start difficult things.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lessons from 8 hours of video edit, across 5 days</title>
      <link>https://leslietang.com/posts/5-days-of-video-edit/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://leslietang.com/posts/5-days-of-video-edit/</guid>
      <description>Outline 5 days. 8 hours. incremental changes. lessons learnt. That&amp;rsquo;s the essence that I want to communicate.
 Start by learning the bare minimum to make something.  How do you determine the bare minimum? Open up the application of your choice Find a video about the general workflow Try it out   For me, my current workflow consist of  Choose the concept Get a rough flow for the concept Choose a music that fits the concept Import the music Trim the music into a suitable duration to work with Choose your videos Import the videos Trim the videos into clips Create Sequences from those clips Add in Sound Effects Add in adjustment layers  for global adjustments, i.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Refining the Outline</title>
      <link>https://leslietang.com/posts/outline-to-draft/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://leslietang.com/posts/outline-to-draft/</guid>
      <description>5 Days of Video Edit
Essence of the Video About starting something difficult. About my takeaway from starting something difficult. About my strategy going ahead.
Title Brainstorm  How to start doing something difficult? How to learn something difficult?  Keywords: difficult, learn, do, try, experiment, process, system, framework
YouTube Title, Thumbnail Starting something difficult. For me, that is starting a YouTube channel. Something that I&amp;rsquo;ve thought about for so long.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Short Morning | Visual Story Telling</title>
      <link>https://leslietang.com/posts/video_edit_5/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://leslietang.com/posts/video_edit_5/</guid>
      <description>This time round, I tried creating a simple storyline.
The concept is the &amp;ldquo;Morning before Work&amp;rdquo;.
From the sunrise, to the preparation of the cafe.
To the grabbing of breakfast.
Though the time frame is the same, yet there exist 3 groups of people living very different lives.
The first group have some time to dine in the cafe. The second group have the luxury of working from home. The last group is on the way to office.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Adobe Premiere Pro</title>
      <link>https://leslietang.com/posts/zoom-in-and-out/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://leslietang.com/posts/zoom-in-and-out/</guid>
      <description>Reference: https://youtu.be/8gxRCn0lKWE?t=31
Today, I learned about Adobe Premiere Pro Plugins.
This here, is a plugin that helps you zoom in and out for clips. Without using key frames.
But what&amp;rsquo;s more interesting to me, is that there&amp;rsquo;s plugins in Adobe.
I think I found an opportunity. Building Adobe Premiere Pro Plugin.
Action Plan  Learn tutorials Find repetitive work Create Plugins that&amp;rsquo;s easy to use  Quick Research Adobe Premiere Pro Plugin uses C/C++ and HTML/JS for the User Panel</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>4th Coffee Sequence</title>
      <link>https://leslietang.com/posts/video_edit_4/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://leslietang.com/posts/video_edit_4/</guid>
      <description>This time round, I&amp;rsquo;ve started with the music. And indeed, the process flows much better. And it&amp;rsquo;s more interesting to find clips that mesh an overarching narrative, that also fits the mood.
Took 2 hours for this. Total Experience: 6 hours.
Let the music guide the visuals I think this is the main takeaway from the past 4 days.
Another new thing that I&amp;rsquo;ve tried is the reversal of clips and adjusting the pace of clips.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>3rd Coffee Video Sequence</title>
      <link>https://leslietang.com/posts/video_edit_3/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://leslietang.com/posts/video_edit_3/</guid>
      <description>3rd Video Sequence Spent about 1 hour on this.
Total Time spent playing with Adobe Premiere Pro: about 4 hours.
This time round, I&amp;rsquo;ve experimented with the following
 LUTs  Color look up table. This seems very useful to apply a consistent color and feel across the entire video. Using adjustment layers also make it easy to experiment with different LUTs.
Sound Effects  Experimented with Sound Effects too. Was looking around for free sound effects and stumbled upon https://freesound.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pan Cake Edit</title>
      <link>https://leslietang.com/posts/adobe-premiere-pro-pancake-edit/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://leslietang.com/posts/adobe-premiere-pro-pancake-edit/</guid>
      <description>Pancake Technique. It is a workflow that&amp;rsquo;s useful for large projects with multiple versions and edits.
 Create a &amp;ldquo;Selection Sequence&amp;rdquo;. Basically this sequence contains all the clips, with the respective in and out points set and ready for usage Create a &amp;ldquo;Final Edit Sequence&amp;rdquo;. Show both sequences, one over another, in the timeline panel Drag clips from Selection Sequence down to the Final Edit Sequence  Label used clips with a different color to prevent confusion   If there&amp;rsquo;s revision needed, CREATE A NEW SEQUENCE!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Second Attempt at Video Edit</title>
      <link>https://leslietang.com/posts/video_edit_2/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://leslietang.com/posts/video_edit_2/</guid>
      <description>Second video sequence attempt: https://youtu.be/fcXv1gw3SHU
This time round it took about an hour.
Had remembered the mistake about sequence settings. This time round it&amp;rsquo;s a HD version. But had forgotten to set Codec, which slows down the rendering during edit.
Remember to Set Sequence Rendering Codec Experimented with Transitions. Movement and blur effects. It didn&amp;rsquo;t exactly went as I expected, nonetheless, it&amp;rsquo;s still an attempt. Would need to research more about transitions and adjustment layers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About Sequence and Shortcut Keys</title>
      <link>https://leslietang.com/posts/adobe-premiere-pro-notes/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://leslietang.com/posts/adobe-premiere-pro-notes/</guid>
      <description>Shortcut Keys You can view the available short keys from Settings &amp;gt; Keyboard Shortcuts
Ripple Trim w, q They basically cut, delete, and close the gap between the cut
Add Cuts ctrl + k
Increase Height of Audio and Video Track alt +/- : increase/decrease audio track height ctrl +/-: increase/decrease video track height
Audio Gain Select the clip and use g
Control Speed ctrl + r: to bring up the clip speed and duration panel</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Attempt at Video Edit</title>
      <link>https://leslietang.com/posts/video_edit_1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://leslietang.com/posts/video_edit_1/</guid>
      <description>My first video sequence attempt, using Adobe Premiere Pro. https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=TLrUc7GaoAA
Some of the challenges encountered.
1. Finding the appropriate clips The difficulty is finding the right clips that will express the ideas I have in mind.
I&amp;rsquo;ve also made a mistake on the sequence settings. Somewhere along the process, I&amp;rsquo;ve set the sequence to be 1280x720 instead of 1920x1080. It&amp;rsquo;s too much of a hassle to redo everyone on 1080p so I ended up uploading a 720p video.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Premiere Pro Basic Workflow</title>
      <link>https://leslietang.com/posts/notes-about-adobe-premiere-pro/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://leslietang.com/posts/notes-about-adobe-premiere-pro/</guid>
      <description>I wrote down the steps from the class by Jordy Vandeput on Skillshare. For me, video edit is a pain, mainly because of the sheer number of actions in the UI.
After going through the first video, I realized there is a logical design decision behind Adobe Premiere Pro. That logical flow becomes obvious, once you understand the general workflow.
General Workflow All video edits start with the bin. The bin contains all the relevant resources.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
