<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>video edit on Leslie TANG</title>
    <link>https://leslietang.com/tags/video-edit/</link>
    <description>Recent content in video edit on Leslie TANG</description>
    <image>
      <url>https://leslietang.com/papermod-cover.png</url>
      <link>https://leslietang.com/papermod-cover.png</link>
    </image>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 21 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://leslietang.com/tags/video-edit/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>4th Coffee Sequence</title>
      <link>https://leslietang.com/posts/video_edit_4/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://leslietang.com/posts/video_edit_4/</guid>
      <description>This time round, I&amp;rsquo;ve started with the music. And indeed, the process flows much better. And it&amp;rsquo;s more interesting to find clips that mesh an overarching narrative, that also fits the mood.
Took 2 hours for this. Total Experience: 6 hours.
Let the music guide the visuals I think this is the main takeaway from the past 4 days.
Another new thing that I&amp;rsquo;ve tried is the reversal of clips and adjusting the pace of clips.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>3rd Coffee Video Sequence</title>
      <link>https://leslietang.com/posts/video_edit_3/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://leslietang.com/posts/video_edit_3/</guid>
      <description>3rd Video Sequence Spent about 1 hour on this.
Total Time spent playing with Adobe Premiere Pro: about 4 hours.
This time round, I&amp;rsquo;ve experimented with the following
 LUTs  Color look up table. This seems very useful to apply a consistent color and feel across the entire video. Using adjustment layers also make it easy to experiment with different LUTs.
Sound Effects  Experimented with Sound Effects too. Was looking around for free sound effects and stumbled upon https://freesound.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Second Attempt at Video Edit</title>
      <link>https://leslietang.com/posts/video_edit_2/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://leslietang.com/posts/video_edit_2/</guid>
      <description>Second video sequence attempt: https://youtu.be/fcXv1gw3SHU
This time round it took about an hour.
Had remembered the mistake about sequence settings. This time round it&amp;rsquo;s a HD version. But had forgotten to set Codec, which slows down the rendering during edit.
Remember to Set Sequence Rendering Codec Experimented with Transitions. Movement and blur effects. It didn&amp;rsquo;t exactly went as I expected, nonetheless, it&amp;rsquo;s still an attempt. Would need to research more about transitions and adjustment layers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Attempt at Video Edit</title>
      <link>https://leslietang.com/posts/video_edit_1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://leslietang.com/posts/video_edit_1/</guid>
      <description>My first video sequence attempt, using Adobe Premiere Pro. https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=TLrUc7GaoAA
Some of the challenges encountered.
1. Finding the appropriate clips The difficulty is finding the right clips that will express the ideas I have in mind.
I&amp;rsquo;ve also made a mistake on the sequence settings. Somewhere along the process, I&amp;rsquo;ve set the sequence to be 1280x720 instead of 1920x1080. It&amp;rsquo;s too much of a hassle to redo everyone on 1080p so I ended up uploading a 720p video.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
