<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"><channel><title>Leslie Tang</title><link>https://leslietang.com/</link><description>Recent content on Leslie Tang</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 26 Apr 2022 19:35:02 +0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://leslietang.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>About OKR</title><link>https://leslietang.com/posts/about-okr/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Apr 2022 19:35:02 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://leslietang.com/posts/about-okr/</guid><description>Introduction to OKR Objectives are stretch goals that are somewhat reasonable. They should inspire, not deflate morale.
Key Results are metrics. When achieved, objectives will be met. They are specific. They are measurable. They give a sense of progression. There should be qualitative and quantitative results.
Key Results are also a basis for check-ins. Weekly. Monthly. Quarterly. As frequently as needed.
We can assign color code to our Key Results for ease of visualization.</description></item><item><title>Why Did I Waited So Long</title><link>https://leslietang.com/posts/why-did-i-waited-so-long/</link><pubDate>Sun, 24 Apr 2022 20:18:28 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://leslietang.com/posts/why-did-i-waited-so-long/</guid><description>The beliefs I have about writing.
Writing should be done with a target audience in mind Writing should be structured Writing should create value A poorly structured writing without a target audience in mind would be messy. And messy writing does not create value. That&amp;rsquo;s why I should not write.
The paradox is that I will never know which writings are valuable until I created them. Value is only assessable in hindsight.</description></item><item><title>Why do I Write</title><link>https://leslietang.com/posts/why-do-i-write/</link><pubDate>Sun, 24 Apr 2022 19:50:09 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://leslietang.com/posts/why-do-i-write/</guid><description>I am already writing in private - notes, scraps, etc. My private writing style only make sense to me, by improving my writing, I would be improving my understanding.
I chance upon two articles -
&amp;ldquo;Learning in Public&amp;rdquo; by swyx https://www.swyx.io/learn-in-public At some point people will start asking you for help because of all the stuff you put out. 80% of developers are “dark”, they dont write or speak or participate in public tech discourse.</description></item></channel></rss>