<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Leslie TANG</title>
    <link>https://leslietang.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Leslie TANG</description>
    <image>
      <url>https://leslietang.com/papermod-cover.png</url>
      <link>https://leslietang.com/papermod-cover.png</link>
    </image>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 18 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://leslietang.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Attempt at Video Edit</title>
      <link>https://leslietang.com/posts/first-video-sequence-attempt/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://leslietang.com/posts/first-video-sequence-attempt/</guid>
      <description>My first video sequence attempt, using Adobe Premiere Pro. https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=TLrUc7GaoAA
Some of the challenges encountered.
1. Finding the appropriate clips The difficulty is finding the right clips that will express the ideas I have in mind.
I&amp;rsquo;ve also made a mistake on the sequence settings. Somewhere along the process, I&amp;rsquo;ve set the sequence to be 1280x720 instead of 1920x1080. It&amp;rsquo;s too much of a hassle to redo everyone on 1080p so I ended up uploading a 720p video.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Emotions</title>
      <link>https://leslietang.com/posts/emotions-in-games-development/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://leslietang.com/posts/emotions-in-games-development/</guid>
      <description>Joy of discovery.
I want to incorporate that element into my game. Something like Kaizoku Oujo, episode 5.
I want to somehow incorporate emotions, or triggers of emotions, within my game.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Non-linear Progression</title>
      <link>https://leslietang.com/posts/non-linear-progression/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://leslietang.com/posts/non-linear-progression/</guid>
      <description>Progression on Web Landscapes should not be seen as Linear.
While new advancements are built on old advancements, the potential for progression is never linear.
It only seems linear after abstraction. After drastic simplification.
In fact, many things are often not linear. But are presented linearly.
Let me define linear in a diagram A -&amp;gt; B -&amp;gt; C
In reality, things would probably look more like A -&amp;gt; B A -&amp;gt; B1 B1 -&amp;gt; C B1 -&amp;gt; C2</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Notes about Atomic Habits</title>
      <link>https://leslietang.com/posts/atomic-habits-notes/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://leslietang.com/posts/atomic-habits-notes/</guid>
      <description>The thing that I often hear about Atomic Habits, is the system that gives you 37x growth in a year.
When I hear about 1% improvements, compounded across the year, I thought it sounded difficult to improve in the samething 1% daily. And I thought 37x growth in one year sounds even more daunting.
The first thing that comes into mind is that this claim is as absurd as those that claim to make X% returns on Y amount, through Forex daily.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Web 3.0 Braindump</title>
      <link>https://leslietang.com/posts/web-3.0-braindump/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://leslietang.com/posts/web-3.0-braindump/</guid>
      <description>Recently I keep seeing about Web 3.0.
I don&amp;rsquo;t know what it is, that&amp;rsquo;s why I&amp;rsquo;m researching it.
https://internationalbanker.com/technology/what-is-web-3-0-and-why-does-it-matter/
https://www.finextra.com/blogposting/3003/web-30-and-40
https://techcrunch.com/2021/09/16/cryptos-networked-collaboration-will-drive-web-3-0/
Ok, the more I read, the more confusing it gets.
The definition of Web 3.0 changes depending on when the article is written.
The recent trends that I heard about Web 3.0 are mainly due to blockchain technologies.
Things get confusing when concepts from humanities and social sciences gets in.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Minimum Viable Writing</title>
      <link>https://leslietang.com/posts/minimum-viable-writing/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://leslietang.com/posts/minimum-viable-writing/</guid>
      <description>I was reading &amp;ldquo;Writing Tools&amp;rdquo; by Roy Peter Clark, to gain some insights that will help me write better. Tool 24 about working from a plan stood out to me.
Minimum Viable Writing In the book, Roy cited an interesting example. About readings being able to get the story and the gist of the writing, the essential parts of the writing, from the headings and subheadings alone.
In other words, from headings and subheadings, we can quickly determine if the idea presented would be valuable, or not.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Premiere Pro Basic Workflow</title>
      <link>https://leslietang.com/posts/notes-about-adobe-premiere-pro/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://leslietang.com/posts/notes-about-adobe-premiere-pro/</guid>
      <description>I wrote down the steps from the class by Jordy Vandeput on Skillshare. For me, video edit is a pain, mainly because of the sheer number of actions in the UI.
After going through the first video, I realized there is a logical design decision behind Adobe Premiere Pro. That logical flow becomes obvious, once you understand the general workflow.
General Workflow All video edits start with the bin. The bin contains all the relevant resources.</description>
    </item>
    
    
    
  </channel>
</rss>
