<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Starting a Daunting Task on Leslie TANG</title>
    <link>https://leslietang.com/categories/starting-a-daunting-task/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Starting a Daunting Task on Leslie TANG</description>
    <image>
      <url>https://leslietang.com/papermod-cover.png</url>
      <link>https://leslietang.com/papermod-cover.png</link>
    </image>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 23 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://leslietang.com/categories/starting-a-daunting-task/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Lessons from 8 hours of video edit, across 5 days</title>
      <link>https://leslietang.com/posts/5-days-of-video-edit/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://leslietang.com/posts/5-days-of-video-edit/</guid>
      <description>Outline 5 days. 8 hours. incremental changes. lessons learnt. That&amp;rsquo;s the essence that I want to communicate.
 Start by learning the bare minimum to make something.  How do you determine the bare minimum? Open up the application of your choice Find a video about the general workflow Try it out   For me, my current workflow consist of  Choose the concept Get a rough flow for the concept Choose a music that fits the concept Import the music Trim the music into a suitable duration to work with Choose your videos Import the videos Trim the videos into clips Create Sequences from those clips Add in Sound Effects Add in adjustment layers  for global adjustments, i.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Refining the Outline</title>
      <link>https://leslietang.com/posts/outline-to-draft/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://leslietang.com/posts/outline-to-draft/</guid>
      <description>5 Days of Video Edit
Essence of the Video About starting something difficult. About my takeaway from starting something difficult. About my strategy going ahead.
Title Brainstorm  How to start doing something difficult? How to learn something difficult?  Keywords: difficult, learn, do, try, experiment, process, system, framework
YouTube Title, Thumbnail Starting something difficult. For me, that is starting a YouTube channel. Something that I&amp;rsquo;ve thought about for so long.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
